<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Medusa Changelog</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sentient06/Medusa/master/changelog.rss</link>
    <description>Most recent changes and updates</description>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.2.0B3</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <div style="font-family: 'Helvetica'; font-size: 0.9em;">
            <h1>Medusa 1.2.0B3</h1>
            <p>
                This is the second of the heavily updated versions of Medusa. It is **NOT** backwards compatible. This version took some user reviews into account.
            </p>
            <h2>New features</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>Support for SheepShaver</li>
                <li>Ability to import existent preferences</li>
                <li>Ability to '''really''' kill the emulator's process</li>
                <li>Ability to delete the NVRAM file</li>
                <li>Partial support for keycodes file</li>
                <li>Ability to resolve path of files that moved or were renamed</li>
                <li>Display emulators' list according to ROM file, then first available emulator</li>
                <li>Toggle button per line in the VM's list window, instead of buttons in the footer</li>
            </ul>
            <h2>Under the hood</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>Major re-factoring to detect emulator's supported models</li>
            </ul>
          </div>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure
                               url="https://github.com/sentient06/Medusa/releases/download/v1.2.0b3/Medusa.1.2.0b3.dmg"
                              type="application/octet-stream"
                            length="4043885"
                   sparkle:version="3"
              sparkle:dsaSignature="MCwCFGea0QuGjY4DVg1C8J/w8IzdtuCLAhR+67Io+zFZWYJcFbah4GEdyVPVSQ=="
        sparkle:shortVersionString="1.2.0B3"
      />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.2.0RC1</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <div style="font-family: 'Helvetica'; font-size: 0.9em;">
            <h1>Medusa 1.2.0RC1</h1>
            <p>
                This is the Release Candidate 1. It should be backwards compatible with v1.2B3.
            </p>

            <h2>New features</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>Complete help book</li>
                <li>Emulators now are saved with path aliases</li>
                <li>The bundle's size is 2MB smaller thanks to less resources (reduced images)</li>
                <li>The application is now automatically flagged as "low resolution" on retina displays</li>
                <li>Medusa can now report proper migration issues' messages</li>
                <li>Ability to open Assets Manager from Virtual Machines' list window</li>
            </ul>

            <h2>Under the hood</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>Lots of code for migrations and some workarounds for missing data.</li>
            </ul>
          </div>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure
                               url="https://github.com/sentient06/Medusa/releases/download/v1.2.0rc1/Medusa.1.2.0rc1.dmg"
                              type="application/octet-stream"
                            length="2827888"
                   sparkle:version="4"
              sparkle:dsaSignature="MCwCFFap/2zM1StSIQfOEhp7P4yu40agAhQX9vWGMX1PJbiR8LmCHjath4Tc1g=="
        sparkle:shortVersionString="1.2.0RC1"
      />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.2.0RC2</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <div style="font-family: 'Helvetica'; font-size: 0.9em;">
            <h1>Medusa 1.2.0RC2</h1>
            <p>
                This is the Release Candidate 2. It should be backwards compatible with v1.2B3 and v1.2RC1.
            </p>

            <h2>New features</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>Added help book access within the application</li>
                <li>Better-looking DMG window</li>
            </ul>

            <h2>Under the hood</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>Help book is accessed by using anchors instead of pages</li>
                <li>Code is once again backwards compatible with XCode 4.2 at Snow Leopard. It is supposed to be compiled for 64-bit but it should work also for 32-bit</li>
            </ul>
          </div>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2015 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure
                               url="https://github.com/sentient06/Medusa/releases/download/v1.2.0rc2/Medusa.1.2.0rc2.dmg"
                              type="application/octet-stream"
                            length="2607144"
                   sparkle:version="5"
              sparkle:dsaSignature="MCwCFA4ZiMloDEeTpLbqYcCwviDgdL6YAhRn0DZX8rcCH4f9zJrzz8xisB9j+A=="
        sparkle:shortVersionString="1.2.0RC2"
      />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.2.0RC4</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <div style="font-family: 'Helvetica'; font-size: 0.9em;">
            <h1>Medusa 1.2.0RC4</h1>
            <p>
                This is the Release Candidate 4. It should be backwards compatible with v1.2RC3, v1.2RC2, v1.2RC1 and v1.2B3.
            </p>

            <h2>New features</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>In the disk settings for the virtual machine, the disk list is more intuitive and the table size can be changed to allow readability.</li>
                <li>Added option to type manually configuration options for the virtual machine</li>
                <li>Added option to type manually configuration options for all virtual machines that run with a specific emulator</li>
                <li>Added option to type manually global configuration options for all virtual machines</li>
            </ul>

            <h2>Under the hood</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>Fixed bug that would parse invalid disk files as valid</li>
                <li>Fixed bug that would freeze the tool that looks for valid emulator binaries</li>
                <li>Fixed bug that would make ROM files unreadable without MacROMan, be unable to parse ROM files without extensions and make the application unusable in Yosemite</li>
            </ul>
          </div>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure
                               url="https://github.com/sentient06/Medusa/releases/download/v1.2.0rc4/Medusa.1.2.0rc4.dmg"
                              type="application/octet-stream"
                            length="3618725"
                   sparkle:version="6"
              sparkle:dsaSignature="MC0CFQCUog47DOrqffJ7G/ejUqWPzmNYqAIUYJATXC40pbyCJ5eoFJsWiWyW/MQ="
        sparkle:shortVersionString="1.2.0RC4"
      />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.2.0RC5</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <div style="font-family: 'Helvetica'; font-size: 0.9em;">
            <h1>Medusa 1.2.0RC5</h1>
            <p>
                This is the Release Candidate 5. It should be backwards compatible with v1.2RC4, v1.2RC3, v1.2RC2, v1.2RC1 and v1.2B3.
            </p>

            <h2>New features</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>In the disk settings for the virtual machine, the disk list now shows whether the disk is bootable or not</li>
                <li>In the disk settings for the virtual machine, the disk now can be set as diskette or CD-ROM to address issues with media that boots only as CDs or diskettes like some installer disks</li>
                <li>In the assets manager, disks tab, a drop-down list was added to flag the selected disk as a hard drive, diskette or CD-ROM; the changes propagate to all virtual machines as they are inherent to that disk image</li>
                <li>In the assets manager, disks tab, a checkbox is now available to manually override the bootable flag; the old bootable flag defines if Medusa found a bootable header, which is a problem in most ISO 9660 disks</li>
                <li>There are icons to all files listed in the assets manager</li>
            </ul>

            <h2>Under the hood</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>Some issues with valid disk images failing to be imported were fixed</li>
                <li>Fixed bug that would mix up the "go to file" (magnifier) buttons from the ROM files tab and the Disk files tab</li>
            </ul>
          </div>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 nov 2016 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure
                               url="https://github.com/sentient06/Medusa/releases/download/v1.2.0rc5/Medusa.1.2.0rc5.dmg"
                              type="application/octet-stream"
                            length="2860631"
                   sparkle:version="7"
              sparkle:dsaSignature="MC4CFQCHLkVoWgevXXBpEuD5np3iR27GywIVAI6KcjstJbmNCSYP7hmtOPa7Y2sF"
        sparkle:shortVersionString="1.2.0RC5"
      />
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
